popafrica.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy | PopAfrica

**Website Privacy Policy**  
POP AFRICA Media, Inc., together with its partners and affiliates, owns, operates, or provides a network of interactive services and applications (together, “POP AFRICA”, “we”, “us”, “our”). This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you access the services, applications, and other features or functionality (collectively, the “Service”) on any website that we own, operate or provide (“Site”) and/or via an application accessible on a mobile device (an “Application”) that includes an authorized link to this Privacy Policy. We receive information about you from various sources, including through your use of the Service and from various third party websites and other services. When you use the Service, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Service after such amendment constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as amended. Any capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meaning given to them in our Terms of Use.

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information, such as your name, username, password, age, and email address, (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you access the Service. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any other sites, services and applications, including Facebook, Google+ and Twitter (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Service, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. While we attempt to provide access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

What Information Do We Collect?

The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our Service. We collect the following types of information from our users.

Personal Information Collected Automatically:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Service. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. If you access the Service through an Application, we may also collect your location information if you have selected settings that enable us to collect such information.

Generally, our Service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the Service so that we can improve and make the Service appealing to as many users as possible, and improve. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use the Site and Application. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Service, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience.

Sign-In Information Collected:

By creating an account or by signing in for the Service using a Third Party Service (as discussed below), you may provide us certain Personal Information, and you may allow others, including us, to identify you. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Service. You may unsubscribe from certain of these messages through instructions in the emails we send you, but certain communications, such as important information regarding the Service are not subject to unsubscription.

Financial Information:

We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the”Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

Third Party Services:

As mentioned above, we may allow you to link your accounts to Third Party Services, such as Facebook, Google+ and Twitter (“Third Party Accounts”) to the Service. If you elect to link to such Third Party Services, we may collect information related to your use of that Third Party Service, such as access tokens made available by that Third Party Service, and other content or information that is provided to us from that Third Party Service. For example, we may receive additional information about you through that Third Party Service, such as gender, age, education, occupation, hobbies, interests, relationship status, and zip code. Third Party Services may also have the ability to restrict the information that is provided to us. Moreover, we don’t actually store your passwords for those Third Party Accounts. Instead, we just use an authentication token to verify your user name.

Any information that you elect to distribute through any of these Third Party Services by using the Service is instantly provided to such Third Party Services and, after leaving our servers, becomes accessible by such Third Party Services. Therefore, in addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, you should also review the privacy policies and terms of use of the Third Party Services that you access through the Service.

Email Communications:

We may receive email activity data from your personal email provider. We use this data to understand and enhance our email communications and the Services. If you do not want to receive email from us, you can unsubscribe from specific email communications or all email communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in any email we send to you. Please note that certain communications, such as important information regarding the Service are not subject to unsubscription.

Cookies:

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. Our cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your email address is.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways.

Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons:

We and our authorized third party partners may use device identification, cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and communications to consumers. This advertising is sometimes called interest-based or online behavioral advertising. Such advertisements are generally targeted and served to particular users (as described in more detail below) and may come from third party companies called “ad networks”. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Services.

Interest-based advertisements may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category, may be based on anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user (including Personal Information such as gender or age), may be based on usage patterns of particular users on the Services, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. Ad networks may set cookies through our Site that enable them to retarget you on other sites.

If you would like an ad network to not set or use cookies on your computer or mobile device, you can visit the following site http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ .

Will We Share Any of the Information We Receive?

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We may share your Personal Information only as described below.

Internal Use: We use Personal Information to deliver certain aspects of the Service to you, to contact you when necessary, to respond to your inquiries for additional information, to provide you with additional information according to your preferences, and for our other business purposes. Sometimes Personal Information may be used to send you information about services, and forums that are available at the Site or other websites. At your election at any time (“opt-out”), you may choose to stop receiving future communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in an email we send you.  
Third Party Services: As discussed above, the Service allows you to connect with certain Third Party Services. When you broadcast information to such Third Party Services, such information is no longer under the our control and is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third parties.  
Non-Private or Non-Personal Information: We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, with service providers, and other persons with whom we conduct business. These service providers and other persons may also share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.  
Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: In certain situations, business with whom we become affiliated may sell items or provide promotions to you through the Service. In other situations, we may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.  
Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.  
Promotional Offers: We may send you offers on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not want to receive offers from us, you can unsubscribe from specific email communications or all email communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in any email we send to you. Please note that certain communications, such as important information regarding the Service are not subject to unsubscription.  
Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.  
Protection of Us and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.  
Is Personal Information About Me Secure?

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your Personal Information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees and third parties who have agreed to be bound by confidentiality restrictions, such as consultants, may be permitted to access Personal Information, and they may do so only for permitted business purposes. In addition, we use SSL encryption in the transmission of your sensitive Personal Information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your Personal Information.

If you access a Third Party Service via the Service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that Third Party Service. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other websites. When linking to another website, you should read the privacy policy stated on that website.

We want you to feel confident using the Service and endeavor to protect your Personal Information we hold in our records. However, no system can be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their Personal Information and should avoid sending Personal Information through insecure e-mail.

What Personal Information of Mine Can I Access?

You can change or access your Personal Information directly through the Service or for information maintained by Third Party Services, through that Third Party Service, such as Facebook Connect.

Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service

What Choices Do I Have?

You can use many of the features of the Service without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect.  
If you do not want to receive email communications from us, you can unsubscribe from specific email communications or all email communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in any email we send to you. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Service, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. Please note that certain communications, such as important information regarding the Service are not subject to unsubscription.  
Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of Personal Information and other information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Service or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Service after such changes have been first posted.

Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Service you may contact us at the email or physical address listed on this Site. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: OCTOBER 1ST, 2014
